{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is his favourite sports team?",
      "answer1": "A) Supersport United",
      "answer2": "B) Mamelodi Sundowns",
      "answer3": "C) Kazer Chefs",
      "answer4": "D) Orlando Pirates",
      "correct": "D) Orlando Pirates"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is his biggest fear?",
      "answer1": "A) Flying",
      "answer2": "B) Frogs",
      "answer3": "C) Snakes",
      "answer4": "D) Heights",
      "correct": "D) Heights"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is his favourite childhood memory?",
      "answer1": "A) Playing arcade games",
      "answer2": "B) Riding his bike",
      "answer3": "C) Being a Soccer Captain",
      "answer4": "D) Being a Volleyball Captain",
      "correct": "D) Being a Volleyball Captain"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is his favourite song?",
      "answer1": "A) No Woman No Cry by Bob Marley",
      "answer2": "B) Stairway to Heaven by Led Zeppelin",
      "answer3": "C) Don't you Worry Child by Avicii",
      "answer4": "D) You'll Never Find by Lou Rawls",
      "correct": "D) You'll Never Find by Lou Rawls"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is his dream vacation destination?",
      "answer1": "A) Hawaii",
      "answer2": "B) America",
      "answer3": "C) China",
      "answer4": "D) Jamaica",
      "correct": "D) Jamaica"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is his favourite food?",
      "answer1": "A) Pap and Chicken",
      "answer2": "B) Steak",
      "answer3": "C) Sushi",
      "answer4": "D)Pasta and Mince",
      "correct": "B) Steak"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is his biggest pet peeve (annoyance)?",
      "answer1": "A) Slow drivers",
      "answer2": "B) Jay-Walking",
      "answer3": "C) People who talk on the phone while driving",
      "answer4": "D) People who left over-take on the road",
      "correct": "B) Jay-Walking"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the worst thing he had to overcame?",
      "answer1": "A) Being sent to prison",
      "answer2": "B) Getting into a car accident",
      "answer3": "C) Getting accused of starting a fire which burned down a house",
      "answer4": "D) Getting accused of splashing a partner with an acidic substance",
      "correct": "B) Getting into a car accident"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is his biggest accomplishment?",
      "answer1": "A) Building a house",
      "answer2": "B) Starting a business",
      "answer3": "C) Winning an award",
      "answer4": "D) Buying a sports car",
      "correct": "A) Building a house"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the biggest amount he ever got in his account?",
      "answer1": "A) R1 000 000",
      "answer2": "B) R284 000",
      "answer3": "C) R470 000",
      "answer4": "D) R157 000",
      "correct": "D) R157 000"
    }
  ]
}